I'm coming up for air.
I'm thirsty.
Is that a crime?
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
I'm waiting for someone.
Lana Lang.
Very original.
I hear she's single again.
They post that on our official stalker website?
I'm not stalking you.
You just have her entire schedule memorized for fun.
That girl's got so many guys telling her
she should qualify for Secret Service protection.
Hi.
Very smooth.
Maybe in about ten years,
you'll actually be able to get a complete sentence out.
I'll catch you later.
Bye.
Hello?
Hi.
Welcome here.
Sorry.
Hi.
Somebody save me
Let your wounds break right through
Don't care how you do it
Just stay, stay
Come on
I've been waiting for you
I've made this whole world shine for you
Just stay, stay
Come on
Don't care how you do it
No problems, Mr. Warner.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah, nah
Forget it!
Uh,еноir's all etc.
Liz, get your thing away from their Sh crec.
Totally get it!
I got it, all that support.
Want to talk about the last couple days?
Jack Palin tried to get the keyword,
First Identity Animal or something out of strange or sleeve,
But I got it.
No, I didn't.
other than the meteor rock labeled Freak Lake next to his body.
You remember that field trip we took down to Crater Lake?
The one where I dropped so gracefully my keys off of a pier?
Yeah, I thought you were gonna call the Navy SEALs.
Jake fished them out for you.
Right, and he was underwater for six minutes.
Now, unless you're David Blaine or a Himalayan yoga master, that's impossible.
Hey, what's with the list?
It was just my hunches, you know?
Sort of anything that's off the charts.
It's kind of a purgatory before you graduate to the wall of weird.
You have a full file of Jake?
Well, I started suspecting a while ago that he had amphibious abilities
due to the meteor rock exposure for a while.
You don't think you might be stretching with this one, Chloe?
I don't think Jake is a mysterious one.
I mean, don't you think it's a little strange?
Rifle-wielding commando shows up right when Lana's getting attacked?
If you want to help track down the enigmatic vigilante,
I would be willing to explore the Jake angle.
That would be assuming
I'm not the one who's going to get it.
I actually had a job here.
Yeah, it was never clear about whose choice
it was for you to quit.
Look, Clark, I could say that I'm swamped with the Daily
Planet column, but the truth is it would just be really
nice to have you back.
All right, Doctor.
I'll have Lex stop by for an examination
by the end of the week.
All right.
And Bob, thanks.
Lex, welcome back to Luther Corp, son.
Feels like I never left.
You'll have the office next to mine.
You've got the Riverview.
I appreciate the gesture, but I'm
not here to enjoy the scenery.
I'm here to generate profits.
Lex, Lex, you already have the job.
And now you've entered the executive ranks,
you need to fill out some paperwork.
Coffee?
I'm good.
Corporate life insurance?
Standard for all upper level employees.
Is $50 million standard?
Don't underestimate your own value, my son.
You seem reluctant, Lex.
I don't understand.
It's hard not to consider the implications
when your mortality has a dollar sign attached to it.
No, Lex.
I'd hoped we'd moved beyond this distrust reflex of yours.
Let's call it common sense.
No, no.
You're a corporate asset, Lex.
Something should happen to you.
The company needs to be compensated for its loss.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
All right.
That's unacceptable to you.
I understand.
You can give your security card to Nelson on your way out.
Hey, Lana.
How you doing?
Hi.
I haven't seen you in a while.
That might be easier that way.
Easier on whom?
I didn't come here to upset you.
I'm doing a story on Jake for the Torch.
That's great.
Clark, what do you want to know?
Well, you told the police you had a friend with him
when he approached you.
And I was wondering if you could point him out.
I think that's him.
Van McNulty.
Thanks.
Glad I could be of help.
Lana.
I'm sorry.
Is this on or off the record?
I'm sorry I haven't stopped by.
Clark, I know we're not together anymore, but you don't need an excuse to come see me.
Hey, so we can rule out the Himalayan yoga master to check out what my connection at
the coroner's office gave me.
You're not going to see any of this in Jake's official autopsy report.
I'm sorry.
Believe it or not, they're gills.
That's disgusting.
Personally, I find the gaping bullet wound more disturbing.
OK, if that shooter hadn't shown up when he did, I'd be dead.
So forgive me if I don't have more sympathy for the gill boy who tried to drown me.
Jake was exposed to the meteor rocks.
He didn't ask for them.
No, just like Gregg Arkin didn't ask to become a bug boy.
And Tina Greer didn't ask to become a bone-warfer.
Look.
The fact is.
their powers, they went psycho and tried to kill me. Tina even came back for seconds.
Chloe's been attacked by more of these people than me. You remember Justin Gaines and Sean
Kelvin? Yeah. One tried to psychically impale me with farm implements and the other just wanted
my body heat. Thanks for the memories. I'm just saying a shot in the head is a little more extreme.
What about all the times that you've saved us from these people, Clark? What makes you so different
from this shooter? For starters, I've never killed anyone. Then how do you explain Tina Greer?
The police found her body impaled in the alley. What happened to her she did to herself.
I was protecting you. Spoken like a true vigilante.
Miss Sullivan, what a nice surprise.
Have you brought me an addendum to your report on Clark Kent?
It's my final article for the Daily Planet. I'm turning in my resignation today.
Oh. Our agreement is terminated. I'm sorry, but Clark's friendship just means too much to me.
I can't say it's unexpected, but it will be disappointing.
Sorry, Mr. Luther. I guess some people are just better at leading double lives than others.
You misunderstand me, Miss Sullivan.
I'm not the one who's going to be disappointed. That'll be your father.
What does he have to do with any of this?
I guess he wanted to surprise you. Your father just made a sizable down payment on a new house overlooking the golf course.
My dad still hasn't paid off the new water heater. I seriously doubt he's moving us to Brad Flat.
Well, it must be his way of celebrating his new promotion. When I rewarded him for his hard work and his dedication to Luther Corp,
he was just brimming with pride.
He'd be devastated if he suddenly found himself unemployed.
You can't do this, Dan.
Yes, I can. But I won't, which is why I think we are going to enjoy a long and fruitful partnership, Miss Sullivan.
Van McNulty?
Hey, Clark Kent.
Hey, Mr. MacDonald.
I'm Mr. MacDonald.
Come on.
Sorry to hear about your friend Jake.
Thanks.
You know, he's always chasing girls,
but I still can't believe he attacked anybody.
Police scanner.
I just want to hear when they catch Jake's killer.
I'm doing a story for the Torch.
Just wondering if you could give me some background on Jake.
Everything I know is in the police report.
I've never seen so many medals before.
Is that your dad?
Must be a real hero.
He was.
And he was a great father.
We used to do everything together.
I'm going to be late for class.
Hey, remember the rock that was tossed next to Jake's body
with the word freak written on it?
Wasn't the first one the police found.
Meet Leonard Wallace, local mechanic
gunned down two weeks ago.
Someone put the similar rock next to his body.
Why do you think he was killed?
I can't be sure about that.
But last month when my VW Bug was in the shop,
I swear I saw his arm reach for a wrench three feet
under my car.
I started a file on him just in case he had some sort
of stretching abilities.
But unlike Jake, Wallace never went psycho.
Yeah.
Well, Smulana's mystery hero isn't out to save anyone.
He's hunting them.
Smulana's own version of a hate crime.
But why?
Revenge.
Van McNulty's father was a marine recruiter
who was killed by Tina Greer.
Tina's dead, so he decides to go Terminator on the rest.
Van's fighting his own personal war.
Cluck, I copied those ideas.
They don't know why youulied this.
The guy like him will be fine.
He's hoodwinked by Feproof.
Would he be able to stop me?
Maybe.
Whatever seems amons?
That's the game.
Bring the car in?
ydia C어가?
Yeah.
slave friend of mine I!
He Denn Gingerbakis!
You little strive-wh
Hello!
형 again and again.
Jez.
Lemon Pledge.
All right, Clark, that's enough.
Let's go.
There's nothing here.
He's pretty tight with his dad.
Clark, last time I checked, there's no offense
in father and son bonding.
Pete, there's a serious arsenal in here.
Clark, it's a hunting cabin.
What do you expect?
I know something's off with your dad.
I could help.
Whoa, what's Lex Luthor's picture doing there?
Pete called the sheriff.
Lex, get down!
Someone's trying to kill us!
Get him inside!
Go!
All right!
Move it! Move it!
Let's go!
You're one of them.
If I saw you catch that slug, it was in your hand.
What are you, some kind of bulletproof freak?
What's wrong?
Does this stuff make you sick or something?
Look at you.
Having a nice big bite of meteor rock.
How's that feel?
How'd you know someone was going to try to kill me?
It's the same person who shot Lana's attacker.
What would he want with me?
Look, I know this is going to sound bizarre, but this kid Van,
he's convinced that the meteor rocks in Smallville have altered certain people.
What do you mean by altered?
He thinks they've developed different abilities than the rest of us, and he's hunting them.
Alexi had a hit list.
They found it in his cabin, and you're on it.
Clark, the only abilities I have are playing the market and falling for the wrong women.
What?
He's...
obviously crazy.
There must be some reason he picked me.
Think about it, Clark.
Lex survived the meteor shower, a near-fatal car accident, and a plane crash.
Even he doesn't have enough money to afford a guardian angel with that much clout.
Check this out.
Lex's medical records show that he has a white blood cell count that is off the charts.
I mean, it's more than enough to raise an eyebrow.
You've been keeping a file on Lex, too.
Chloe, didn't you learn your lesson about keeping your secret files?
They're my own private notes.
Since when is curiosity a crime?
Since someone took your database and turned it into a personal hit list.
Van had a printout of the same file on his bulletin board.
Van helped network half these computers.
He must have cracked my password.
Oh, God, Clark.
This is all my fault.
Chloe, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to blame you.
It's not like you pulled the trigger.
No.
I just loaded the gun and pointed it in the right direction.
Where is he?
Lex.
Thank God you're all right.
You're now covered by my personal security.
I appreciate the gesture, Dad,
but I'm not about to let some adolescent assassin disrupt my life.
Don't take that cavalier attitude, Lex.
I wouldn't worry about it, Dad.
I'm sure of it now.
I'm sure of it.
Not yet.
There's some difficulty getting you underwritten by Lloyds of London.
On what grounds?
Your tendency to attract near-death experiences has made you too great a liability.
I would think surviving would count for something.
You're right.
I'll get it straightened out.
Don't worry.
Dad.
Before the meteor shower,
I had one way or another to do long hours of work.
Double-targeted fast-track troop Level 8 fireworks.
There was no option.
Hey.
How've you been lately, свет?
I uploaded the traits.
Some of those have against my terms.
What am I supposed to do?
You should recover soon.
I'm sure Ethan will soon recover soon.
He's probably on a retreat now.
I can do two things for him.
You better come back soon.
I obviously inherited strong genes.
Sheriff Adams, have you found Van yet?
Yeah, we're keeping an eye out,
but there's no reason to think he's come back to Smallville.
I think there is. Take a look at this.
One of these people will be Van's next target.
Are we in the psychic business now, Mr. Kent?
Just look at the first three names.
Where'd you get this?
A friend of mine who believes that these people
are linked to a certain phenomenon in Smallville.
A phenomenon, huh?
It's a little out of my jurisdiction.
Well, you don't have to believe it's true.
Van McNulty does, and these people are in a lot of danger.
Can't hurt to be cautious.
I know.
They're all going to get hurt.
How's Lex doing?
Okay, I guess.
It's not the first time he's been in the crosshairs.
Are they sure Van was the shooter?
I am.
Lon, I know he saved your life,
but I don't think that was his intention.
No, it was just a happy accident.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it like that.
Clark, I really thought I was going to...
I'm gonna die.
You've been through worse.
Because you've been there to protect me.
But I knew you weren't coming this time.
So when Van showed up, I guess I was just relieved that there
were others like you out there.
He's not like me.
You have to see him for what he is.
He's a killer.
Lana, it's OK to be mad at people who tried to hurt you.
But it's not fair to take it on everyone who's
been affected by the meteors.
It's not their fault. No one has to be different.
Life would just be so much better for everybody
if the meteor shower never happened.
37, 198, 199.
Hiya.
Oh, a tremendous amount of help.
Yeah.
boa.
Sorry.
We just lost contact.
I hope nothing ever happens to you during your stay.
OK?
I'm sorry.
I've searched everywhere from here to Metropolis.
It's like Van disappeared.
Oh, Clark, he can't hide forever.
Every police officer in the state's looking for him.
He'll find him.
Let's hope he doesn't find his next target first.
Dad, do you think I'm like Van?
I think you know my answer to that question, son.
The real question is, do you think you're like Van?
I've come into contact with a lot of kryptonite-infected people, and...
it never ends with us being friends or shaking hands.
I gave a lot of this whole tolerance speech.
I always assumed the worst about them, too.
I don't know.
For all we know, there could be lots of people out there who've been infected,
who lead perfectly normal lives.
They're forced to live with their secret, just like me.
And they could be using their abilities for good, too.
I'm gonna get cleaned up.
Mark?
Mark!
Dad!
I got you.
There!
No!
How's that coming, sweetheart?
I got it.
It's okay.
It's all right, Clark. Hang in there.
It's okay. It's all right.
Jonathan, he's dying.
The poison is spreading so fast.
Okay, Clark, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get it out.
Clark, Clark, you gotta stay still, son.
Hold on, baby. Hold on. Dad's gonna get it.
Oh, my God.
He's not breathing.
All right. There we go, son.
Don't you give up on us now, son.
Kevin! Kevin!
Martha's in there so far.
Wait a second.
I think I got it.
Okay.
Okay, hold on, baby. He's got it.
Get that thing out of here.
Clark, come on, son.
Come on, Clark.
Come on.
Let's put this guy in his limit.
You're almost two.
Come on, no.
Come on.
Yeah, yeah, let's play any national park.
Yeah, let's play any national park.
Let's play any national park.
© BF-WATCH TV 2021
You may have survived one bullet,
but I'm not gonna make that mistake again.
Lana, let her go.
Not until she sees once and for all
that her lover boy's a freak show.
Ah!
I told you he was a freak.
You're a freak.
Ah!
Clark, how did you...
It's all about dressing
for the occasion.
For the occasion.
What is that?
Lead?
You can rest a bit easier.
Van McNulty's been taken into custody.
He's in the psychiatric ward.
I knew Van was misguided,
but I'm not so sure he's insane.
What makes you say that?
Churchill once said,
out of intense complexities,
intense simplicities emerge.
Maybe that kid was right about me.
Lex, he's a fanatic.
But Chloe Sullivan's not?
How many times have I come face to face with death
and walked away without a scratch?
I've practically lost count.
Weirder things have happened.
All this time, I thought the reason
I survived that Porsche accident was because of you, Clark.
Now I'm not so sure.
See, I've always tried to explain everything
by looking outside myself.
But maybe the truth lies inside my own physiology.
Maybe I am a freak.
Lana, is everything okay?
I thought we established that we didn't need a reason
to come and see each other.
I didn't get a chance to tell you,
but you really kicked ass yesterday.
You know, some hero I turned out to be.
He still got shot.
I don't know what's left to say
You must be pretty sore.
All of the dreams of yesterday
Still stings a little.
What's on the outside?
Can you say?
Or am I getting kissy?
You know, I, um...
I believed Van for a minute when he told me you were bulletproof.
Is that what he told you?
It was really comforting to hear.
Suddenly everything made sense.
The tornado.
All the times that you've been there.
Everything I can't explain.
I wish the answer was that easy.
But I wasn't infected by the meteor rocks.
If you were...
It would be okay.
I'm getting on.
But what's the use?
You know how I get.
I can't decide which is the right way.
I have to get back to work.
What I don't understand
is you're willing to walk into bullets for me,
but you won't share what's going on inside.
Clark, if you don't open up to the people that love you,
you'll all die.
You'll always be alone.
I can't believe you want to spend your life like that.
I may not have a choice.
You always have a choice.
I can't decide.
If we pass time
For one last try
So it's goodbye again
Bye
You hid a glitch?
Miss Sullivan?
I know a very capable computer technician
who might have some familiarity with your setup.
How could I be so idiotic?
You donate the computers and then send your experts in to set them up.
Yeah, philanthropy.
I've always prided myself on that.
What about tampering with a high school student's personal computer?
I think you'll find your personal computer is on loan to the school
as the property of the Luther Corp Foundation.
You are so low, you're subterranean.
You know, Clark's files aren't even on this hard drive.
Do you really think I'd be that stupid?
My interest doesn't end with Clark Kent.
I'm intrigued by your whole body of work.
I hate to see your valuable research evaporate into the ether,
but I will not allow information that concerns my son
to be made available to anyone who can hack their way into your personal files.
Mr. Luther, I'm very sorry about what happened to Lex.
These files were never meant to be seen by anyone other than me.
I warn you,
if I ever catch you investigating a member of my family again,
a computer,
or a glitch,
will be the least of your problems.
Good night, Miss Sullivan.
You better know where this fun's going.
You got all kinds of types of old-coffee now.
Uh, anyway, I want to thank you.
issemostly. Vinny got a really cool A-Z for this last one of the nine hours,
but you never really know what to expect when you're gonna almost lost.
Where's thekeys, then?
Wait, huh?
They're all here.
Sorry if your elevated your そうね
that's the Hermit disguised into a donkey.
Ankh testicles big picture doing.
Vanity can't be quite the same without money...
Really, buddy?
Is there a secret way you'd've never seen before?
There can't be a secret way.
Every major spiritualby the Earth,
one of them is full of things,
it's like a character that cannot be found in its Jabba-Rabbit nest,
Thank you.